good job.
お疲れ様
That's a hotel tool.
それはあれですね、ホテルの道具ですね
Because it feels a little girly,
ちょっと ガーリーな感じだから、
I was wondering something.
何かと思っちゃった
It was fluttering all the time, so I thought it might be surgery.
一周ひらひらしてるから、なんか手術かなと思って
No, it's a tool.
じゃないよね、道具ですよね
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
はい、お疲れ様です
I want to do a bonus video now.
今から特典映像やりたいんですよ
Bonus footage, bonus footage, special footage,
おまけ映像、特典映像、スペシャル映像、
A strange picture.
おくざらしい映像
I'll pass this on.
これを渡します
Please take this.
これを受け取ってください
It's our present.
僕らのプレゼントです
rotor.
ローター
A true pink rotor.
まさにピンクローター
If only the rotor wasn't pink.
ローターでもピンクじゃなかったらね
But at that time, it was called green rotor or yellow rotor.
でも、その時はグリーンローターとかイエローローターって言わ
No, right?
ない でしょ?
surely.
確かに
Only pink rotors are called pink rotors.
ピンクローターだけピンクローターって言うんですよ
I understand?
わかります?
I would like you to masturbate using this.
これを使ってオナニーをしてもらいたいんですけど、
Earlier, I attacked with a demo that wasn't about masturbation,
さっきはオナニーじゃなかったデモで攻めましたけど、
This is the one I used at home.
自宅で使ってたやつですね
Yes, exactly.
そうですね、まさに
Please make it feel like you were in elementary school.
小学校の時の感触物にしてください
This is a classic in elementary school, please.
小学校の時の定番で、これってやつお願いします
I'm also keeping an eye on things.
僕も様子を見守ってますよ
Start already.
もう始めて
Please do it already.
もうやってください
Please do it at all.
全然やってください
Don't worry about my existence.
気にせず僕の存在なの
It's going to be pretty intense.
結構激しく行くんだね
Did you go?
行ったの?
I just went.
今行ったんだ
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
I didn't really understand it.
うずによくわからなかったよ
You went quietly.
地味に行ったのね
Twitching.
ピクピクと
Isn't it amazing?
すごいじゃないですか
I'm sorry.
すいませんでした
I had no idea until I saw it just now.
ちょっと今目が合うまで一応わからなかったです
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Do you remember?
思い出した?
To a woman when she was a young girl.
幼い少女の頃の女に
Do you remember?
思い出しました?
Yes, just a moment.
はい、ちょっと
It feels fresh.
新鮮な気持ちでね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
yes.
はい
Gratch, gratch.
グラッチ、グラッチ